question_data =  [
    {"type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "category": "Vehicles",
     "question": "The Chevrolet Corvette has always been made exclusively with V8 engines only.",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},

    {"type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
     "question": "Nutcracker Suite was one of the musical pieces featured in Disney&#039;s 1940&#039;s film Fantasia.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},

    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science: Gadgets",
     "question": "The Western Electric Model 500 telephone uses tone dialing to dial phone numbers.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Geography",
     "question": "Seoul is the capital of North Korea.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Animals",
     "question": "&quot;Kamea,&quot; the Gilbertese Islander word for dog, is derived from the English phrase &quot;Come here!&quot;",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Geography",
     "question": "The surface area of Russia is slightly larger than that of the dwarf planet Pluto.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "History",
     "question": "If you grab the bladed end of a longsword in a specific way, you will not cut yourself.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "David Baszucki was a co-founder of ROBLOX Corporation.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Geography",
     "question": "There exists an island named &quot;Java&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "History",
     "question": "The Korean War ended in 1953 without any ceasefire.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "Scottish producer Calvin Harris is from the town of Dumfries, Scotland.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
     "question": "Blue Danube was one of the musical pieces featured in Disney&#039;s 1940&#039;s film Fantasia.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "The planet Mars has two moons orbiting it.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Art",
     "question": "Venus of Willendorf is one of the earliest works of art, depicting the planets Mars and Venus embrace in the heavens at night.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Sports",
     "question": "Tennis was once known as Racquetball.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
     "question": "Pneumonoultramicroscopicsilicovolcanoconiosis is a synonym for the disease known as silicosis.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "History",
     "question": "The first televised presidential debate was between Jimmy Carter and Gerald Ford.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Art",
     "question": "Pablo Picasso is one of the founding fathers of &quot;Cubism.&quot;",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Furby was released in 1998.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Kissing someone for one minute burns about 2 calories.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
